<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Next Wojtyla Night on Wojtyla Night</title>
    <link>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Next Wojtyla Night on Wojtyla Night</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 13:23:29 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is Wojtyla Night?</title>
      <link>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 12:23:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>What is Wojtyla Night?#Wojtyla Night is an event inspired by the life of Pope St. John Paul II (born Karol Wojtyla). It is an evening when we gather together as a community to share those things which evoke the transcendentals of truth, goodness, and beauty, all things which may be called &amp;ldquo;catholic&amp;rdquo; (in the small-c sense). After sharing a meal, we participate in something which is part open-mic night, part poetry slam, part art show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wojtyla Night 1</title>
      <link>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/archive/wojtylanight1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 21:56:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/archive/wojtylanight1/</guid>
      <description>Wojtyla Night#Hosted by Faith Noah and Michael Schattle at Faith&amp;rsquo;s apartment
 &amp;ldquo;St. Crispin&amp;rsquo;s Day Monologue&amp;rdquo; from Shakespeare&amp;rsquo;s Henry V, Michael Schattle &amp;ldquo;Take it to the Root&amp;rdquo; (Original Poem), Alex Lohn (photo below) Original Songs, Luke Bellet Original Songs, Mariana Barron Esper Art Journal + Original Poem, Nick McCann with Musical Accompaniment by Zachary Larson St. Joan of Arc Monologue, Emily Martinez JPII Theological Excerpt, Rachana Chhin Polish Dances on Fiddle, Rae Corrigan Dramatic Performance of &amp;ldquo;The Raven&amp;rdquo; by Edgar Allen Poe, Johnny Knoebel &amp;ldquo;Love (III)&amp;rdquo; by George Herbert, Oliver Ha There&amp;rsquo;s a Wideness in God&amp;rsquo;s Mercy (Hymn), Faith Noah + Oliver Ha Holy Water Blessing in Latin, Fr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wojtyla Night 2: Incarnation</title>
      <link>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/archive/wojtylanight2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 22:25:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/archive/wojtylanight2/</guid>
      <description>Wojtyla Night 2: Incarnation#Hosted by Alex Lohn at his Apartment. The theme of this event was &amp;ldquo;Incarnation&amp;rdquo;.
 &amp;ldquo;Only at Christmas Time&amp;rdquo; by Sufjan Stevens, Alex Lohn Marian Hymn, Dennis Hodapp &amp;ldquo;Boil Them Cabbage Down&amp;rdquo; and other fiddle tunes, Rae Corrigan Painting: &amp;ldquo;Annunciation&amp;rdquo; by Beatrice Emma Parsons, Garrett McMillan &amp;ldquo;Manifesto: The Mad Farmer Liberation Front&amp;rdquo; by Wendell Berry, Adrienne Prochaska From a homily by St. John Chrysostom: Office of Readings, First Friday of Lent, Johnny Knoebel Original Songs, Mariana Barron Esper  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wojtyla Night 3: Feast of St. Benedict</title>
      <link>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/archive/wojtylanight3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 12:19:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/archive/wojtylanight3/</guid>
      <description>Wojtyla Night 3: Feast of St. Benedict#Hosted by Alex Lohn and Paul Davies at Benedict&amp;rsquo;s Bungalow (their house).
 Amazing Grace + Blackbird by the Beatles, Paul Davies Reading from the Desert Fathers + I Have Made Mistakes by The Oh Hellos (with added original verse), Alex Lohn Reading from the Rule of St. Benedict + Sweet Home Alabama by Lynyrd Skynyrd, Rhett Jones Fiddle Tunes, Rae Corrigan &amp;ldquo;Conway&amp;rsquo;s Game of Life&amp;rdquo;, a Computer Simulation, Nate Meyers Holy Sonnets VI-X by John Donne, Michael Schattle Poetry Reading, Becca Kee &amp;ldquo;Make You Feel My Love&amp;rdquo; by Bob Dylan, Madeleine Stoll &amp;ldquo;Tortoise&amp;rdquo; (Original Painting), Julian Richardson Excerpts from &amp;ldquo;The Ballad of the White Horse&amp;rdquo; by G.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wojtyla Night 4</title>
      <link>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/archive/wojtylanight4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 12:22:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/archive/wojtylanight4/</guid>
      <description>Wojtla Night 4#Hosted by Cathedral Young Adults at St. Mary Cathedral in Austin, TX
 Reading from John Paul 2&amp;rsquo;s Letter to Artists + Original Stained Glass, Michael Schattle Song, Alex Lohn &amp;ldquo;The Weight of Mass&amp;rdquo; by Josephine Nobisso, Becca Kee &amp;ldquo;God&amp;rsquo;s Grandeur&amp;rdquo; by Gerard Manley Hopkins, Jessica MacNair Song, Mad Stoll and Nicole Heger Original Song, Luke Bellet Original Poetry in Mixed Languages, Joseph Vasquez Exhibiting Two Paintings on Archetypal Sacrifice, Garrett McMillan Songs, Dennis Hodapp Original Song, Mariana B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wojtyla Night 5: In the Park</title>
      <link>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/archive/wojtylanight5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 12:20:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/archive/wojtylanight5/</guid>
      <description>Wojtlya Night 5: In the Park#Hosted by Rhett Jones at Butler Metro Park in Austin, TX.
 Wayfaring Stranger, Rhett Jones Gavotte by Bach, on violin, Jessica MacNair Original Poetry, Alex Lohn Bluegrass Guitar, Louis Grace Irish Ballad, Mad Stoll &amp;amp; Nicole Heger Song, Mad Stoll Original Poetry, Sean Chamberlain Poetry/Monologue, Johnny Knoebel Original Poetry, Nick McCann Original Children&amp;rsquo;s Story, John Weaver Classical Guitar, Alvaro Davila Recitation of the Aeneid in Ecclesiastical Latin, Joseph Vasquez Short Story, Laura Woodson Original short story, Garrett McMillan &amp;ldquo;Derethil and the Wandersail&amp;rdquo;, a short story by Brandon Sanderson, Cody Crosby Original Music, Luke Bellet  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wojtyla Night 6</title>
      <link>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/archive/wojtylanight6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 12:21:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/archive/wojtylanight6/</guid>
      <description>Wojtyla Night 6#Wojtyla Night 6
Hosted by Cathedral Young Adults at St. Mary Cathedral in Austin, TX.
 Selections from &amp;ldquo;The Jeweler&amp;rsquo;s Shop&amp;rdquo; by Karol Wojtyla, Michael Schattle &amp;ldquo;The General&amp;rdquo; by Dispatch, Rhett Jones Original Poetry, John Weaver Original Song, Mariana B Collaborative Art Piece, Nick McCann and Alex Lohn Original Poetry, Fr. Will Rooney Original Poetry, James Obute Original Paintings and Prints, Catholic Art with Environmental and Social Justice Themes, Hannah Loveland &amp;ldquo;Where the Soul Never Dies&amp;rdquo;, Traditional Song, Jessica MacNair and Louis Grace Original Poem, Nick McCann Original Poetry, Maria Schloeder Original Poetry, Louise V Original Poetry, Alex Lohn Exhibition of Paintings, Garrett McMillan Latin Poetry Recital, Joseph Vasquez Original Poetry, Dane Macaulay Improvisational Song, Ethan Original Song, Luke Bellet  A Poem by Nick McCann#I dedicate this poem to the time we have with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/pages/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 12:22:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/docs/pages/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact Page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Journal</title>
      <link>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/posts/newjournal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 13:23:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mpschattle.github.io/wojtyla/posts/newjournal/</guid>
      <description>Some folks have been proposing that we collect some of the works presented at Wojtyla Night into a quarterly publication. We could add to them some book reviews, spiritual reflections and other articles written by folks at St. Mary Cathedral.
Does anyone have interest in this project?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
